### HUYNH KIM HAN

#### **PROFIL**

Multilingual Office Administrator with 3+ years of experience seeking a role in a multinational company. Possessing strong organizational, communication, and data analysis skills, I am confident in my ability to contribute to a diverse and global team



KIM.HUYNH1195@GMAIL.COM



+84869791195



#### AUSBILDUNG

Bachelor's degree from the University of Social Sciences and Humanities

Major: German Linguistics and Literature – German Economy and Tourism

Certificate: Corporate Accounting

#### SKILLS

**GERMAN. ENGLISH** 

MICROSOFT OFFICE

TIME MANAGEMENT

**DATA ANALYSIS** 

**DRAFTING** 

#### **EXPERTISE**

**PAYROLL** 

**E-INVOICE** 

**INSURANCE** 

RECRUITMENT

ASSET MANAGER

### **EXPERIENCE**

# ADMINISTRATION INNORIX LLC - KOREA COMPANY

- Contact the supplier to set up presentation rooms for internal departments.
- Organize onsite and offsite events.
- $\bullet$   $\,$  Support HR in the onboarding and offboarding activities.
- Cost Management, Office Services & Supplies.
- Follow the boss's request

#### LOCAL INC

нсмс

03/2024 -06/2024

## ADMINISTRATION SG SAFETY VINA COMPANY LIMITED - KOREA COMPANY

- Contact the supplier to provide the service to the company and upload the order to the system.
- Receive cost invoice from the supplier, check the legitimacy of the supplier invoices.
- Monitor the payment progress for suppliers against contracts.
- Receive timesheet to calculate revenue and issue debit note to the customer
- Collect purchase invoices and report the cost fee to the manager monthly.
- Make a car rental contract and contract annex.

LOCAL INC

нсмс

06/2022 -08/2023

## GENERAL ADMINISTRATION ATC CONSULTING (VIETNAM) LIMITED COMPANY - SINGAPORE COMPANY

- Ensure smooth and efficient running of the company.
- Arrange bookings for both local employees and foreign visitors.
- Collaborate with vendors and the business team on hiring, onboarding, and status changes.
- Maintain accurate and GDPR-compliant personnel files, information, and data.
- Keep detailed records of employee leaves (annual, sick, etc.).
- Work with vendors to ensure effective accounting processes, internal controls, and legal compliance.
- Process payment requests based on contracts, invoices, and supporting documents.
- Track and manage office petty cash.
- File and store documents, including invoices and receipts, according to accounting and tax regulations.

LOCAL INC

нсмс

10/2020 - 05/2022

## ADMINISTRATOR ASSISTANT - ASSET MANAGER GBC ENGINEERS - GERMAN COMPANY

- Manage the list of suppliers of the asset Office furniture, deliveries and payments, fire protection and prevention
- Save and manage the payment of the company's assets.
- Recruitment of international employees.
- Prepare stationery for newcomers.
- Contact the supplier to set up presentation rooms for internal departments (Marketing, R&D, etc.)
- Help with internal events: Women's Day, Fruit Day, Christmas event, YEP, ...
- Staff the office with administrative tasks such as scanning, copying, delivering documents
- Register parking with the building owner and employee card.

LOCAL INC

нсмс

09/2019 - 06/2020

### VOLUNTARY SOCIAL YEAR ARBEITERKIND - GERMAN COMPANY

- The main part of the work consists of teaching the children to read and write.
- Support in a fixed class assistants during lessons: playing, supervising, reading, ...
- Participation in school trips, events at school.
- Teaching assistance in individual courses
- Participation in parents' evenings and parent-teacher meetings.

LOCAL INC

**GERMANY** 

09/2018 - 09/2019